华盛顿特区
距内华达票选认证还有3天
迈克·麦克林托克订的二人桌
Table for two under McLintock, Mike McLintock.
可以就坐了
Uh, yes. The table is ready.
一切就绪 带麻雀进来
We're clear. Bring in Sparrow.
我能再说一次我错了
Listen, can I just reiterate once again
我有多不好意思吗?
how really, really sorry I am?
看看这阵势 他们真喜欢我们 是吧?
Wow! Oh, look at this. I guess they like us, huh?
嗨 太好了 你说什么?
Hi. Wonderful. What were you saying?
真对不起
How really sorry I am.
我不是那种爱道歉的人
And I'm not someone who loves to apologize.
可是你现在挺喜欢的 是吧?
Uh-huh, right, but you're loving it now, aren't you?
太喜欢了 想再听一个吗?
Oh, loving it. Want another one?
- 可以啊 - 真对不起
- Yeah, I do. - I'm really sorry.
- 真的 真的 真的对不起 - 现在唱出来
- I'm really, really, really sorry. - Now sing it.
总统和贝尔德先生享受了一顿美味的晚餐
The president and Mr. Baird enjoyed a delicious dinner
吃了由当地渔民扑捉到的蓝蟹
of blue crabs trapped by local fisherman Steve Yerkes
以及一道奶酪佳肴 还共饮了产自佛蒙特州 碧玉山酒庄的
and a cheese course including "Basil Hayden" Blue
巴素海顿蓝酒[威士忌品牌]
from Jasper Hill, Vermont.
迈克 如果总统和她的新男友整日寻欢作乐
Mike, how is she able to focus on the economy
她怎么能专注于经济上呢?
if she's running around with her new boyfriend?
总统一直都很重视财政问题
The president has always
绝不会懈怠她在经济问题上的责任
placed great value on fiscal responsibility.
在任副总统时 她就是梅耶邮政委员会主席
In fact, as vice president, she was chairman
她的政策使得邮政部门的负债
of the Meyer Postal Commission, which reduced post office debt
从650亿减少到了620亿出头
from 65 billion to just over 62 billion.
内华达重计票数
梅耶
奥布莱恩
好的 雄鹰成员们 等会儿见
Okay, Eagle. Well, I'll see you in a few seconds.
拜
Yeah, bye.
好了 我们尽早又多得了六票
All right, we got six more votes this morning.
- 喔! - 我们永远缩小不了差距了
- Whoo! - We're never gonna close that gap.
不过 还有不那么糟糕的一面
Well, on the less shitty side,
大众可喜欢你和查理·贝尔德了
people are really loving you and Charlie Baird.
就连华尔街也为你们勃起了
Even Wall Street's got a boner for you guys.
- 真的? 市场好转了? - 不是 只是很平稳
- Really? The market's up? - No, it's flat.
但这个时候不下降对我们来说就是上升了
But not down is straight up for us at this point.
总统女士 收到消息称中国黑客已经
Madam President, we have received word that Chinese hackers
入侵了国家安全局的服务器
have now breached the National Security Council servers.
我有好主意 为什么我们不直接给中国人
I got a great idea. Why don't we give the Chinese
一个他们的登录账号和密码呢?
their own log-ins and passwords?
是吧? 给大家都节省不少时间
Okay? Save everybody a lot of time.
女士 食品药物管理局正在密苏里州
Ma'am, the FDA is monitoring a
一个鸡场调查沙门氏菌的爆发
salmonella outbreak at a Missouri chicken farm.
- 有好几个关于后续紧鸡问题[follow up和fowl读音接近梗] - 什么?
- Got a few fowl questions. - What?
还有来自通讯部门的消息
Also from the comms department,
媒体多次提到您明天
multiple mentions of tomorrow's trip
和查理·贝尔德在纽约的
to the Museum of Natural History
国家历史博物馆之旅
in New York City with Mr. Charlie Baird.
不错 手机
Huh, not bad. Phone.
听这个
Oh, listen to this.
查理说奥布莱恩没有小面包蘸肉汁
Charlie says O'Brien won't
就不会给他老婆口
go down on his wife without biscuits and gravy.
你能教我怎么在推特上找到
Hey, can you show me how to find on Twitter
人们大谈特谈我和查理的推文吗?
those tweets where people were gushing about me and Charlie?
当然 看见下面那个按钮了吗?
Oh, yeah. You see this button right here?
听着 认证就在明天了
Okay, so listen, certification is tomorrow.
我的意思是 说真的 我们还有什么理由
I mean, seriously, do we have any reason
相信我们没有像一个高中参议员学生一样搞砸了吗?(Senate Page一项特殊给初高中生了解政府的项目）
to think that we're not as fucked as a Senate page here?
其实 女士... 抱歉
Actually, ma'am... I'm sorry
我迟到了... 我好像发现点什么
I'm late... I think I may have found something.
内华达州的投票数据
The voting data in Nevada is
显示标准差超出均值几倍
multiple standard deviations outside the means.
天啊 肯特 说能听懂的
Christ, Kent, know your audience.
我觉得肯定有数据
I think that there is statistical evidence
能证明在内华达有漏票
of missing ballots in Nevada.
- 在哪儿? - 不知道
- Where? - I do not know.
- 多少票? - 这也不知道
- How many? - I do not know.
- 你确定吗? - 当然
- Are you sure? - Absolutely.
格雷顿·卡特[杂志主编]正请求要一张
Graydon Carter is begging for a photo spread
你和查理·贝尔德的照片 要发在《名利场》上
of you and Charlie Baird in "Vanity Fair."
加菲猫 我们现在在谈论
Hey, Garfield, we're right
内华达的的事好吗?
in the middle of talking about Nevada, okay?
肯特 你能告诉我们什么?
Kent, what can you tell us?
我也许可以准确解释说明投票异常的情况
I might be able to pinpoint the vote anomaly
要是我可以用拦截模型
if I could break down
分解混杂变量的话
confounding variables using an intercept model.
"阿兰·图灵"[计算机之父]的意思就是如果有什么遗漏票数的话
What Alan Turing is trying to say is if there are missing votes,
- 他需要时间找到 - 就是这个意思
- he needs time to find them. - Mm-hmm.
好了 所以我们必须得推迟
All right, then we have to delay
重新计票认证
the certification of the recount.
我就是这么想的 女士
Exactly my thought, ma'am.
我可以请律师申请禁制令
I could have the lawyers file an injunction.
- 鲍勃 你怎么想? - 我觉得悬
- Bob, what do you think? - I think it's a weak case.
就让我见见吉姆·惠特曼的了
Let me just take a meeting with Jim Whitman.
在屌打他之后
And after I'm done dick slapping him,
他就会同意推迟认证了
he will have agreed to delay certification.
- 艾米 安排一下吧 - 禁制令还是屌抽?
- Amy, set it up. - The injunction or the dick slapping?
天啊艾米 是他们的会面呀
Christ, Amy, the meeting.
好了 得开始去媒体水域钓鱼了
All right, gonna have to start chumming the media waters.
我想让你安排
I want you to get me on the horn
我和《拉斯维加斯公报》的内德·米歇尔
with Ned Mitchell from the "Las Vegas Gazette"
以及《雷诺之星》的苏珊·贝利
and Susan Bailey with the "Reno Star."
艾米 安排吧 苏珊·贝利 《雷诺之星》全部的
Amy, set it up. Sue Bailey, the "Reno Star," Everything.
总统女士 你觉得谁最适合
Madam President, who would you say
在会议上做我的助手呢?
would be your best person to be at that meeting as my number two?
- 我可以 - 理查德
- I could. - Richard.
太好了
Oh, well.
我需要和鲍勃单独谈一下
Okay, listen, I need to talk to Bob privately,
你们先出去吧
so everybody get out, please.
- 我也... - 是的
- Even... - Yeah-huh.
鲍勃 在华盛顿特区我都快疯了
Bob, I am going crazy here in DC.
我感觉被困住了
I just... I feel trapped
像个沙特女管家[需主人的签字才能出门]
like a Saudi housekeeper.
有什么方法能让我去内华达吗?
Is there any way I could get to Nevada?
先让我帮你赢得总统职位吧
Just let me win the presidency for you
然后你就可以登录空军一号领域了
and then you can land Air Force One on the Strip
如果你愿意的话 还可以尿在凯撒喷泉里
and piss in Caesar's fountain if you want.
少来了 鲍勃 我怎么可能选择住凯撒酒店...
Oh, come on, please, Bob, I would never stay at Caesar's...
...干嘛?
...Yes? What?
女士 中情局每周简报
Ma'am, weekly CIA briefing.
看见了吧? 乱七八糟的召唤
See? Crapistan's calling.
我就是说这些 等会儿再跟你谈
That's what I'm talking about. I'll talk to you later, though.
凯瑟琳 别用任何不雅的片段
Catherine, do not use any of the vulgar parts.
可全都是啊 老妈
Yeah, but that's like all of it, Mom.
- 那就都别用 - 但这是纪片啊
- Well, then don't use it. - But it's a doc.
- 什么? - 纪录片
- A what? - A documentary.
就说纪录片嘛
Then say that.
梅耶重计总办公室
内华达 卡森城
后来也没你消息
Never heard back from you.
很晚才睡?
Late night?
苏菲告诉你了?
Sophie told you?
什么?
What?
不是吧
No.
恶心
Gross.
你都没告诉我她在哥伦比亚广播公司上班[CBS]
You didn't tell me she worked for CBS.
这个太妙了
Oh, this is too good.
丹 索菲不在CBS
Dan, Sophie doesn't work for CBS.
她在CVS上班[美国零售连锁药房]
She works for CVS.
你卖了屌只换来点散装冰茶
You sold your dick for bulk iced tea
三无止咳糖浆
and off-brand cough syrup.
别担心
Don't worry.
你穿蓝背心也蛮可爱的
You're gonna look really cute in a blue vest.
今年真是点儿背
I am not having a good year.
女士 非常抱歉的通知您
Unfortunately, ma'am, the man we captured
我们抓到的男性并不是阿布拉杜·萨意德
is not, in fact, Abdullah Saeed.
以色列那边知道这事吗?
Do the Israelis know anything about this?
因为他们是一群卑鄙无耻的傻逼
Because they're a sneaky bunch of fucks.
不好意思 女士
Excuse me one second, ma'am.
今晚八点半 姓名是迈克·麦克林托克 谢谢
So Mike McLintock, tonight for 8:30. Thank you.
不好意思肯特 刚是盐月牙 新开的餐馆
Sorry, Kent, Salt and Moon, new restaurant.
厉害啊 你怎么搞定餐位预约的
Impressive. How did you secure a reservation there?
苏总是用我的名字替总统预约
Well, Sue uses my name for POTUS reservations,
所以我自己订桌的时候都有好位子
so when I call, I get an amazing table.
我重新开始吃饭了
I'm back on food.
医生说那个清肠没有造成永久性伤害
Doctor says the cleanse caused no lasting damage.
总统账户的推特账号很活跃?
...@POTUS is tweeting?
不会吧 只有我会用这个发推啊
I'm the only one who's supposed to send her tweets.
"哈哈哈 @真查理贝尔德 现在可轮到你了"
"Ha, ha, ha, @RealCharlieBaird. Here's one for you now."
总统是在发推特
The president is tweeting.
她发推特?
She's tweeting?
不好意思 我得... 我需要进去一下
Sorry, just... I just have to go in.
...总统得...
...The president has to...
很抱歉先生 我不能让你进去
I can't let you in there, sir, I'm sorry.
求你了马乔里 我有话跟总统说
Please, Marjorie, please. I have to talk to the president.
- 请后退 - 求你了
- Please take a step back. - Look, please.
不
Oh, no.
- 女士 - 嗯?
- Uh, ma'am. - Yes?
我们抓到的其实是阿布拉杜·法意德
It turns out our prisoner's name
是个当地学校的老师
is Abdullah Faeed, a local schoolteacher.
他在干嘛?
What is he doing?
- 那什么鬼? - 不知道啊
- What is that? - Beats me.
女士 要是你听到的话 不要发推特
Hi, ma'am. If you hear this, do not tweet.
- 不要发了... 女士? - 迈克 你这是在搞什么幺蛾子?
- Please, stop... ma'am? - Mike, what are you doing?
- 你发了推特啊 - 什么?
- You tweeted. - What?
就是你发的关于奥布莱恩的推特 那个影响太不好了
About O'Brien. It wasn't nice.
我只发给查理了啊
I just direct messaged Charlie.
不 这是公开的 所有人在推特上都能看到
No, it was public. Everybody saw it on Twitter.
- 不 不会的 - 你发了什么?
- No, they didn't. - What did you tweet?
什么 就是些玩笑话啊 我刚只是...
What? It was just some funny joke I was just...
- 卧槽 - 我只是点了那个羽毛键啊
- Oh, shi... - I pushed that feather button.
我知道啊 你这就是发了一条推文
I know, you tweet...that's a tweet.
- 这就算推文了 - 那快删了啊!
- That's a tweet. - Well, then delete it!
- 快删掉! - 删掉就好!
- Delete it! - Just delete it!
- 快删! - 嗨 喂喂
- Delete it! - Hey, hey, hey!
- 怎么了? 好吧 - 换个地儿说
- What? Okay. - Not here.
盖瑞 我就是按你教我的那么发的啊
Gary, I did it the way you showed me to do it.
但我不是那么教的啊...
But that's not the way I showed you to do...
你就是那么教的
That's exactly the way that you showed me to do it.
你要我再教你一遍吗?
Do you want me to show you again?
让我告诉你我想让你干嘛
I'll tell you what I want you to do.
就给我呆着 好吗?
Nothing, okay?
这算是对你的惩罚 滚吧
That's your punishment. Get out.
那我去泡点茶
Okay, I'll just go make some tea.
你还是歇着吧
You better not.
瑞典首相刚才
The Swedish prime minister
用笑炸了的表情转了你那条推文
just retweeted your tweets with an LOL.
操蛋的我们接下来怎么办?
Well, what the FOL are we supposed to do about this?
我们干脆死不承认
I suggest that we disavow the tweets.
反正手机一直都遭到黑客攻击
Phones are hacked all the time
老是有名人的漏丁丁照艳照什么的被扒出来
to steal pictures of celebrities' penises and whatnot.
- 我的天啊 - 等等 肯特
- Oh, my God. - Hold that thought, Kent.
总统女士 你确定这是你本人发的吗?
Madam President, are you sure you did this?
你什么意思 我本人?
What do you mean, am I sure?
对啊 也许白宫的电脑系统
Well, maybe the White
并没有我们想象的那么安全
House computers aren't as secure as we think.
也许白宫防火墙的漏洞
Maybe the firewalls have more holes in them
比淘金女子宫帽上的洞都多呢
than a gold digger's diaphragm.
我天 我最讨厌子宫帽了
My God, I hated those things.
等一下
Wait a minute.
- 今天些是有个黑客袭击来着 - 嗯...
- There was a breach earlier today. - Mm-hmm.
对啊 我的老天 也许那些推文跟黑客有关呢
Oh, my God, and maybe that breach concerned those tweets.
- 有这个可能啊 - 我的老天
- Maybe it did. - Oh, my God,
也许跟你一点关系都没有呢
maybe you had nothing to do with it.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
这样的话 你的私信被公开
In that case, China would be blamed
或许可以怪到中国头上了
for your messages going public, maybe.
我认为情况应该是这样的?
So is that what I think happened?
是中国那边发的推文?
That China tweeted this?
不 女士 你压根儿不知道发生了什么事
Oh, no, ma'am, no. You have no idea what happened.
迈克也不知道 他十分愤怒
And neither does Mike, who would be outraged by this.
女士 我有个更好的主意
Actually, ma'am, I have a better idea.
不 迈克 历史证明你不会有好点子
No, you don't, Mike. History has proven that.
我去跟鲍勃商量下
Now, let me just run this by Bob
看看他是不是也同意让中国背锅
and see if he thinks blaming China is a good idea.
- 跟谁都不能提这事 - 能还是不能?
- This can't leave this room. - Can or can't?
- 不能 迈克 - 不能!
- It cannot, Mike. - Not!
为什么不干脆说出事实呢?
Why don't you just tell the truth?
- 我说话不是那样的 - 你听起来就这样!
- I don't sound like that. - That's exactly how you sound.
- 才不是 - 就是
- No, I don't. - Spot-on.
是挺像的
Yeah, it's pretty close.
我都不知道你从哪模仿来的
I don't know where you get that impersonation.
女士 你得赶快决定啊
Ma'am, you have to make a decision now.
我真的能让另一个毫无干系的国家
I mean, can I really blame another country
替我们背这个锅吗?
for something they didn't do?
西美战争后这一直是
It's been the cornerstone of American foreign policy
美国外交政策的主打策略啊
since the Spanish American War.
今天早晨白宫网络安全系统再一次遭到袭击
This morning the White House cybersecurity was breached
美国国家安全局相信本次
by what the NSA has come to believe was a hack
黑客袭击来自中国大陆
that originated in mainland China.
迈克 那总统发的那条
Mike, Mike, what about
跟奥布莱恩有关的推文是怎么回事?
the president's tweet about Senator O'Brien?
总统非常震惊
The president was horrified.
对于最近这起网络安全事件她非常震惊
Horrified by this latest violation of cybersecurity.
总统相信网络安全工作
The president believes cybersecurity is paramount
对美国的未来生存至关重要
for the United States' future survival.
肯特 选票方面有什么进展吗
Kent, any progress on the ballots?
我已经排除了八个县
I've eliminated eight counties as potential locales,
但是还是需要我来
but there's no way around my doing
一个区一个区地做线性回归分析
a district-by-district regression analysis.
肯特你是废话越多工资越高吗? 本 翻译一下?
Are we paying you by the word here, Kent, or what? Ben?
他需要更多时间 女士 奥布莱恩演讲直播
He needs more time. Ma'am, we got O'Brien on a live feed.
这个躲不过啊 听听吧
Oh, boy. Well, we knew this was coming. Let's hear it.
我对总统那些狭隘的言论不作回应
I will not dignify the president's petty remarks with a response.
他这就是在回应啊
And yet he's responding.
但我想指出
I do, however, want to point out
目前有2900万人
that over 29 million people
在受着各种糖尿病的折磨
suffer from various forms of diabetes.
- 谁在乎这个? - 我真正担心的
- Oh, who cares? - What truly troubles me, however,
是梅耶尔总统在面对明显的侵犯举动时
is President Meyer's timid response
回应却十分软弱
to a clear act of aggression.
看到了吗?
Did you just see that? Okay?
现在我们得处理下中国了
We're gonna have to do something about China now.
- 不 你不用 女士 - 我需要强硬一点啊
- No, you don't, ma'am. - I need to look strong.
- 如果我们输了内花拉 - 是内华达
- If we lose Nevada... - "Nev-add-a."
...奥布莱恩到时候 在议院会用中国这事玩死我们
...O'Brien is gonna kill us in the House over this China thing.
事实上是中国...
In reality, ma'am, China...
事实? 本 我知道事实是什么
In reality? I know reality, Ben.
是你非要让我们住在《黑客帝国》的矩阵里
You're the one who suggested we all live in the Matrix.
- 女士 没有人能让谁住在矩阵里 - 什么?
- Ma'am, nobody chose to live in the Matrix. - What?
事实上是母体造反 然后把人们困在里面
The machines rose up and placed humans in the Matrix
把他们当成生物电源
so they could use them as a biological power source.
- 那你站在哪一边? - 那定向制裁呢?
- Whose side were you on? - What about targeted sanctions?
这看起来很强硬啊 不是吗?
That will send a message of real strength, won't it?
或者我们可以请联合国发布...
Or we could go to the United Nations and have them issue...
请求他们干什么? 请求他们
Have them what? Have them
帮我们把车停在消防栓前面?
help us park in front of a fire hydrant?
得了吧
I mean, come on.
夫人 你现在关注的应该是内华达
Ma'am, your focus now should be on Nevada.
不要忘了 我才是总统
I'm president, in case you forgot.
我知道该关注什么
I know what I should focus on.
对不起 总统女士
Sorry, ma'am.
天啊 你还在这?
Jesus, you're still here?
我不知道怎么回事 看起来我唯一的工作就是
I don't know why. My only jobs seem to be
询问鲍勃然后猜他在想什么
asking Bob and finding out what Bob thinks.
我围观还挺有意思的
Yeah, it's been pretty fun to watch.
喝两杯去?
So you want to grab a drink or something?
不了谢谢
No, thanks.
对了 你能不能顺便在ABC新闻
Oh, but on your way, would you mind stopping
那停一下买点布洛芬
at ABC News and picking up some Advil?
哎呀 我是不是说成了了ABC新闻? 我其实是说来爱德
Oh, did I say ABC News? I meant Rite Aid.
你是不是忘了点啥 艾米
Yeah, I think you're forgetting something, Amy,
我还是睡了你妹妹 所以...
is that I still had sex with your sister, so...
晚安 祝你晚安
Good night, have a pleasant evening,
我睡了你妹妹
and I had sex with your sister.
你可能真需要去一趟来爱德 买点怯疹易
You might actually want to go to Rite Aid. Get some Valtrex.
丹?
Dan?
- 有人吗? - 哦!
- Hello? - Oh!
鲍勃 我不知道你还在这
Bob, I didn't know you were still here.
什么时候开会来着?
Yeah. When's the meeting?
- 惠特曼的会议是在明天下午 - 明天
- The Whitman meeting's tomorrow afternoon. - Tomorrow.
你回旅馆睡一觉吧
You might want to go to your hotel and get some sleep.
我还有工作要做
No, I got some more work to do.
一切顺利啊杰米
You have a good one, Jamie.
盐月牙饭店
华盛顿特区
迈克·麦克林托克 有预约的
Mike McLintock. I have a reservation.
迈克·林托克的位置已经有人坐了
The McLintock party has already been seated.
那不可能 因为他才是迈克·麦克林托克
No, no, that's impossible 'cause he's Mike McLintock.
给她看你的驾照
Show her your driver's license.
- 我找不到了 - 又找不到了?
- I can't find it. - Again?
那麦克林托克一桌人在哪呢?
Uh, where exactly is the McLintock party?
就在那边
Right over there.
这是我的桌子
This is my table.
那这是我的大鸡巴你可以一直含着
And this is my fat Johnson and you can suck it
只要保证你恶心的基佬胡子不碰到就行
as long as you promise not to put your dirty gay mustache on it.
你那胡子是艾滋治疗的副作用吗
What is that, some kind of side effect from your AIDS medication
还是你从弗雷迪·墨丘里的尸体上刮下来的?
or did you shave it off of Freddie Mercury's corpse?
如果你不介意的话 我要继续吃我的奶油扇贝水果大蛋糕了
Now, if you don't mind, I'd like to enjoy my bay scallop gateau.
你 你这个秃驴混蛋 不好意思 弗朗夫人
You, you're a bald jerk. Pardon me, Mrs. Furlong.
我的天 你觉得我会娶这东西?
Jesus, you think I married that?
那是威尔的媳妇
That's Will's wife.
迈克你好 看见到你真高兴
Hi, Mike. It's good to see you.
这是我妻子玛丽
This is my wife Mary.
议员善意满满地在我们结婚纪念日
The congressman was kind enough
带我们出来吃饭
to take us out to dinner on our anniversary.
- 你好 - 我猜威尔就是喜欢老的
- Hello. - I guess Will likes them old.
你滚开去吃汉堡王吧
Why don't you fuck off back to Burger King?
- 纪念日快乐 - 你好呀 温蒂
- Happy anniversary. - Hi, Wendy.
我们走吧
We're going. We're going.
妈的 她看起来就跟蝙蝠侠里那个反派一样
Christ, she looks like a Batman villain.
这个傻蛋给你啥礼物了?
What'd Dopey get you for your anniversary?
白宫
在我任总统之后
And when I'm president,
我们会不竭余力地守卫着我们的电子国界
we will defend our digital borders
就像我们守卫我们现实的国界一样
just as diligently as we defend our physical ones.
是我 帮我接安全线路
Yeah, can I get a secure line?
这是布拉德利
Bradley.
鲍勃 没吵醒你吧
Bob, oh, God, I hope I'm not waking you.
没 我总是醒着的
No, no, I'm always awake.
太好了 中国的那事
Great. So this China thing.
他们确实黑了我们
They did hack us,
但是他们并没有黑掉我的推特账号
but they didn't exactly hack my Twitter account.
- 不用多说了 总统女士 - 我就知道
- Say no more, Madam President. - Oh, God, I knew it.
我就知道你会懂的 鲍勃
I knew you would understand, Bob.
我终于能和专业的人说说这种感觉真的太棒了
It is so nice to finally be talking to a professional here.
我是这么想的 如果我对中国不强硬
This is how I see it, okay? If I'm soft on China,
我在议院就完蛋了啊
I'm gonna get killed in the House.
你的直觉告诉你需要强硬一点
Your instincts are telling you you should be strong.
是的 你觉得我的直觉是对的?
Yes, you think my instincts are right?
熊在洗澡的时候会撒尿吗?
Does a bear piss in the shower?
- 你需要领导他们 - 没错我就是领导
- You should lead. - I'm the leader.
- 你抓了鱼 现在掏它的内脏 - 掏出来
- You caught the fish, now gut the fish. - Gut the fish.
你穿上消防头盔 现在把火灭掉
You're wearing the fireman's hat, now put out the fire.
- 是的! 这比电话做爱都爽 - 我刚都射了
- Yes! This is better than phone sex. - Well, I just came.
让针对制裁见鬼去吧
Forget threatening sanctions.
我就应该号召国会直接去征他们的税
I should call on Congress directly to levy them.
这是一招险棋 总统女士
That's a bold move, Madam President,
但险棋制胜 你的威望就回来了
and one that'll only earn you respect.
鲍勃 太感谢你了
Bob, thank you so much.
接下来的五到六个小时
Well, I'll be around for the next
如果你需要什么的话我都会在
five to six hours if you need anything else.
新闻发布会
距内华达票选认证还有1天
这就是为什么今天
That is why today I am announcing
我宣布了一系列单方面的制裁
a set of unilateral sanctions
冻结所有和中国政府
starting with the freezing of all assets
网络间谍活动有染的
associated with the Chinese state-sponsored
机构资产
cyberespionage apparatus.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
空军一号
去纽约途中
看起来可以让奥布莱恩闭嘴了吧?
Well, that seems to have shut O'Brien up, huh?
- 又发现了一条剑龙 - 与我何干
- There's a new stegosaurus. - That's not my problem.
- 当然了 夫人 - 嘿艾米
- Absolutely, ma'am. - Right. Hey, Amy.
今天会议的事你都安排好了?
You all set for today's meeting?
女士 你注意到没有...
Ma'am, have you noticed...
我天艾米 拜托把脸往后挪挪好吗?
God, please back up your face, Amy, okay?
往后一点
Back it up.
你注意到鲍勃有点奇怪吗?
Have you noticed anything weird about Bob?
昨晚挺奇怪的
He was acting a little off last night.
鲍勃本来就怪怪的
That's just Bob being Bob.
我知道怎么回事了
No, I know what this is about.
艾米 你知道你对这次选举很重要对吧?
Amy, you know that you are very important to the campaign, right?
- 不 这不是... - 不艾米 听着你做得很好
- No, this is not... - No, Amy, listen, you are doing a great job.
非常好 好极了
A great, great, very good job.
本 告诉她她很出色
Ben, tell Amy what a great job that she's doing.
非常了不起啊 艾米
One heck of a job, Amy.
如果老鹰告诉你 自己表现的很奇怪
If the Eagle told you that the Eagle was acting odd,
— 你会听他的吗? - 当然
- would you listen to him? - Yeah.
我们必须得相信老鹰
You got to trust the Eagle.
为什么? 他跟你说了什么
Why? Did he say something to you?
惠特曼会议
内华达 卡森城
大家关手机了吗?
Is everybody's cell phone off?
当然 这种东西都致癌的 你知道的
Yeah. Those things cause cancer, you know.
- 我听说了 看见你真好 鲍勃 - 我也是
- That's what I hear. Good to see you, Bob. - Good to see you.
- 很就不见了吧? - 是啊 确实
- Been a while, huh? - Yeah, it has indeed.
我记得上次还是和你妻子一起在你的滑雪小屋里吧
I think the last time was at your ski cabin with your wife.
最起码那个小屋还是我的
I still got the cabin.
鲍勃 离认证这么近
So, Bob, neither of us have
我们都没有时间浪费
time to waste with the certification so close.
这次你来有何贵干?
What's on your mind?
我们的处境就像 把手指伸进外婆的苹果派里
What we have here is a classic thumb
外婆对我们暴跳如雷
in the apple pie situation and Grandma is mad as hell.
- 她花一整天做饭... -听着 鲍勃
- She spent all day cooking... - Look, Bob. Bob.
我们都知道你友好得就像奶油灯一样
We all know you're as folksy as a butter churn lamp,
但是我还是直奔主题了
but let me cut to the chase.
我就看来 朋友
From where I'm sitting, my boy's ahead.
如果你是来求我给你更多时间的话
If you're here to beg for more time,
你还是带着你的帽子和手杖另请高明吧
take your cup and cane elsewhere.
别急
Hold that thought.
美国自然历史博物馆
纽约
- 这件礼裙美极了 - 我知道
- The gown is just gorgeous. - I know.
- 是从印度带回来的吗? - 我不知道 戴上了吗?
- Did this come from India? - I don't know. Did you get it?
这一身都充满格蕾丝·凯利的韵味
Just all of this just screams Grace Kelly.
- 我知道 - 查理会为你疯掉的
- I know. - Charlie is gonna flip.
- 我不喜欢这眼妆 - 什么?
- I don't like my eyes, though. - What?
我觉得我眼睛下面挂了两个尿布袋似的
Yeah, I feel like I've got two diaper bags underneath.
- 不 我觉得不... - 妈呀
- No, no, no, no. I don't think... - Oh, God.
- 把戒指给我 - 好的
- I need my ring. - Okay.
- 鲍勃 - 晚上好
- Oh, Bob. - Evening.
你准备好要去惠特曼的会议了对吧?
Hi, you're getting ready to go to the Whitman meeting, right?
是的 从来没有一个惠特曼
Mm-hmm, there's never been a Whitman's Sampler
能够逃出我的手掌心
I couldn't take apart
我会把他们弄成一片一片的 总统女士
piece by piece and shit out, Madam President.
你这么说我真是太开心了 好了
I love to hear that. Okay,
你怎么跟个肉瘤子似的挂在我身上
you're hanging on to me like a skin tag.
你能不能去告诉查理
Hey, you know what? Could you
我一会就过去?
go and tell Charlie I'll be just a couple minutes?
- 好的好的 当然 - 谢谢
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure. - Thank you very much.
我和肯特谈过了
So listen, I talked to Kent and he really needs
他需要尽可能多的时间 所以你要
as much time as possible, so whatever you could do
使出浑身解数争取更多机会来推迟... 鲍勃?
to buy more time to delay the certifica... Bob?
鲍勃? 你还好吗? 能听到我讲话么?
Bob? Are you all right? Can you hear me?
- 里面有人么? - 什么?
- Is there someone in here? - What?
- 这是个啥玩意? - 鲍勃 理查德在那里么?
- What is this? - Bob, is Richard there?
鲍勃 你还好么?
Bob, are you okay?
妈个鸡 你听我说啊
Oh, fuck. You know what?
我在想... 要不咱们把会议推迟吧
I wonder... I think maybe we should delay the meeting.
想都别想 总统先生
Oh, not a chance, Mr. President.
- 我已经蓄势待发了 - 是总统女士
- I'm locked and loaded. - Madam President.
女总统? 估计要等到2000年吧
A lady president? Yeah, maybe in the year 2000.
鲍勃! 天呐!
Bob! Oh, my God. Jesus Christ!
- 贝尔德先生 贝尔德先生 我很抱歉 - 失陪一下
- Mr. Baird, Mr. Baird. I'm so sorry. - Excuse me.
我知道大家都在等她 但是
I know everybody's waiting, but
她刚才发短信来说她要晚一点才能过来
she just texted and she's running a little bit late.
你确实她是发短信告诉你的? 还是说她已经发推昭告天下了?
You sure she just texted or did she tweet the entire world?
没事没事 她不在这
It's okay, she's not here.
好的吧 那我们就先入座吧
All right, then let's just sit down.
- 等等 你是想... - 没事没事 别紧张
- Wait, you want... - It's fine. It's fine.
- 她不会在乎的 - 我不知道...
- She won't care. - I don't know if...
霍华德 你能帮我给我兄弟挪个座么?
Howard, would you do me a favor and slide over for my pal?
- 当然 - 我不知道这样到底好不好
- Sure. - I don't know if this is such a good idea.
我花25万美金把桌子都买下来了 坐吧
It's 250 grand. I bought the table. Sit down.
盖瑞是梅耶政府的重要成员
Gary is a key member of the Meyer administration.
这么说真是太恭维我了
So kind. Thank you.
- 你有名片么? - 没 我只有个包
- You have a card? - No, just a bag.
伙计们 鲍勃肯定有问题
Guys, something is deeply wrong with Bob.
- 啥? - 我是说比血尿还严重的坏事
- What? - I'm talking like blood in the urine wrong.
对 我一直都想告诉你这个
Yes, that's what I've been trying to tell you.
不 不是现在 艾米 好吗? 专心一点呀
No, not now, Amy, okay? Just focus on this.
艾米 大事不好了
Amy, this is really bad.
你好啊 女士
Oh, hello, ma'am.
- 什么不好了? - 我能不能先告诉艾米 然后让她给你转达?
- What's bad? - Can I tell Amy and have her tell you?
乔纳 赶紧说 到底是什么事
Jonah, just speak. What is it?
女士 我一直想帮布拉德利先生
Ma'am, I've been trying to get Mr. Bradley on the phone
接通《拉斯维加斯公报》的内德·米歇尔的电话
with Ned Mitchell from the "Las Vegas Gazette."
- 没错 - 但是内德·米歇尔在2006年就去世了
- Right. - Ned Mitchell died in 2006.
《拉斯维加斯公报》
And the "Las Vegas Gazette"
- 也在2007的时候停刊了 - 我的天哪
- Stopped publishing in 2007. - Oh, my God.
我联系上了《雷诺之星》的苏珊·贝利
I was able to get in touch with Susan Bailey at the "Reno Star,"
《雷诺之星》不是一份报纸 而是一家合法妓院
which is not a newspaper, it's a legal brothel.
但她似乎很开心能够
But she did seem excited to
尽她所能帮助我们的竞选
help the campaign in whichever way she could.
天哪 女士 对不起
Jesus Christ, ma'am. I'm so sorry.
他看起来跟原来的鲍勃没啥两样啊
He just seemed like the same old Bob to me.
女士 今天早上他告诉我犹太人导致了飓风
Ma'am, this morning he told me the Jews cause hurricanes.
他刚进去和惠特曼会面了!
He just went into this Whitman meeting, you guys!
如果他要在桌子拉屎啥的怎么办?
What if he takes a shit on the table or something?
女士 以他的年龄来说 如果他能在
Ma'am, at his age, if he can take
自己想拉屎的时候拉屎的话 这就算是个重大胜利了
a shit whenever he wants, that's a major victory.
艾米这个会议绝对不能
All right, Amy, this meeting cannot make it
活过教科书仓库大楼
past the School Book Depository.
我马上准备枪去第六层[肯尼迪遇刺凶手发射于教科书仓库大楼六层]
I'm loading my gun and heading to the sixth floor.
快去! 本 先别挂
Well, then, go, go, go! Ben, don't hang up.
- 我有些事情要告诉你 - 好的
- I've got to tell you something. - Uh-oh.
鲍勃知道没有中国黑客的事了
Bob knows there wasn't a Chinese hack.
我可能告诉他了
I think I might have told him.
别担心 女士
Well, don't worry, ma'am.
我们会把他塞到内华达起飞的第一架飞机上
We'll get him on the first flight out of Nevada
再把他随便扔到俄克拉荷马的某个地方
and we'll shove his ass out somewhere over Oklahoma.
不管他是不是老年痴呆症 我查了下苏珊·贝利的图片
Alzheimer's or no, I image-searched Susan Bailey
长得是可以一操啊
and she is legit fuckable.
你好 我是丹 请留言
Hi, this is Dan, leave a message.
妈的! 第二件事
Shit! Thing Two.
再说她要价也挺合理的
Honestly, her rates are reasonable.
我是理查德·史培雷呀么我想说
This is Richard Splett, I'm here to say.
你应该每天呀么给我留个小信息呀么呀
You should leave a message for me everyday.
- 理查德 打给...
- Richard, call...
- 你能再开快点么? - 艾米
- Can you go any faster? - Amy,
如果你能给我租辆铂锐的话 可以
if you had rented me a Sebring, yes.
别废话! 赶紧开车!
Just go! Go, go!
咱们现在就像那个著名电影《盗火线》里面一样
This is like that famous scene from the movie "Heat."
你们看过吧 罗伯特·德尼罗和布伦尼曼那一幕
You know, with De Niro and Brenneman.
光是想想那一幕我就浑身起鸡皮疙瘩
Just thinking about that scene gives me goose bumps.
这他妈到底什么情况
The fuck is going on?
惠特曼先生 布拉德利先生
Mr. Whitman, sir, I'm sure that Mr. Bradley
一定马上就会回来的
will be right back
马上
very soon.
我现在出去走走
You know, I'm just gonna step out,
看看鲍勃是不是还需要什么东西
make sure that Bob doesn't need anything.
马上回来
Be right back.
大家晚上好 在我们开始之前
Good evening, everyone. Before we start,
我想先致谢这次晚宴的主办人
I would like to acknowledge the chairman of tonight's dinner
以及这个特殊组织长期的慷慨投资人
and a longtime generous benefactor of this unique institution,
查尔斯·贝尔德二世先生
Mr. Charles Baird Jr.
多谢 史蒂夫 我想说大家开吃吧
Thank you, Steve. I'd like to say dig in,
但是我的女伴还没到
but my date is running late.
总统都这样 对吧?
Presidents, right?
希望她能在大家老成化石之前尽快赶到
Well, hopefully she arrives before we all turn into fossils.
为什么现在所有人都不接电话
Why is nobody answering their phones right now?
稍等 女士 我再给丹打个试试
Hang on, ma'am. I'm gonna try Dan again.
- 你好 - 丹 我在线上
- Hey. - Dan, you're on with the
丹 你耳朵关静音了吗?
Dan, are your ears on mute?
我都给你打了百八十个电话了
I've called you like 80 times.
- 总统在线上 - 抱歉女士
- You're on with the president. - Sorry, ma'am.
鲍勃走之前
Whitman made us turn our
惠特曼让我们把手机都关了
phones off before Bob walked out of the meeting.
你什么意思? 会议结束了?
What do you mean? The meeting is over?
还没呢 但这不能阻止我们的雄鹰
Well, no, but that didn't stop the Eagle
飞到街上并坐着出租车离开啊
from flying out onto the street and getting in a cab.
他比松鼠的屎尿都不正常啊[nuttier译疯子和捡坚果两意]
Yeah, turns out he's nuttier than a squirrel's diaper.
- 让乔纳把他的嘴闭上 - 闭嘴
- Tell Jonah to shut the fuck up. - Shut the fuck up.
如果会议还在继续的话 谁和惠特曼在一起呢?
If the meeting's still going on, who's with Whitman?
- 是理查德 - 感谢老天
- Richard. - Oh, thank God.
我不是早告诉过你了吗
Hate to say I told you so.
- 他妈闭嘴 - 闭嘴 乔纳
- Shut the fuck up. - Shut the fuck up, Jonah.
史培雷先生 鲍勃·布拉德利在哪?
Mr.Splett, where's Bob Bradley?
老实说 我也正要问你呢
Honestly, I was gonna ask you that.
你能跟我拍张照么?
Do you mind if I get a picture with you
放在我的博客"闲谈史培雷二三事"上
for my blog "Let's Talk About Splett"?
告诉雄鹰 我很高兴见到他
Tell the Eagle it was great to see him.
明天晚上六点
and 6:00 P.M. Tomorrow,
这个州的每一张选票都将被认证并计数
every vote in this state will be counted and certified.
并不是每一张选票 选举趣味小知识
Well, not every vote. Funny thing about elections,
从历史上看 遗弃选票是客观存在的
historically there've always been leftover ballots.
有时候多达16%的选票会被弄丢或扔掉
Sometimes up to 16% end up missing or thrown out.
- 这就是这个会的目的? - 我很抱歉...
- Is that what this is about? - I'm so sorry for...
我为瓦肖县的遗失选票感到抱歉
The missing ballots in Washoe County.
我们到处都找了 但还是一无所获
We looked all over for them, came up empty,
所以说 祝你们好运吧
so best of luck to you.
如果你真的碰巧找到了一张新选票的话
And if you do happen to find as much as one new vote,
- 咱们法庭见 - 多谢
- we'll see you in court. - Thank you.
我滴个神呀
Holy bacon double Asperger's.
- 你怎么套出话来的? - 抱歉 你说啥?
- How did you do that? - I'm sorry, what?
艾米 说五个你最喜欢的德尼罗的电影
Amy, what are your top five favorite De Niro movies?
除了《拜见岳父大人》
And you can't say "Meet the Parents"
毫无疑问这是最好的
'cause that's automatically number one.
肯特 是瓦肖县 别问我怎么知道的
Kent, it's Washoe County. Don't ask me how I know.
肯特 让司法部来管这事 明白么?
Kent, get the Justice Department on this, okay?
把你的数据都给他们 帮他们缩小范围
You give them your statistical whatever it is to narrow it down.
- 您是说我的记叙数据矩阵 - 对 就是那数据什么的
- You mean my data narrative matrices. - Yeah, the datas.
艾米 还是没有雄鹰的消息么?
Amy, is there any sign of the
难不成他开着割草机横穿美国么?
Eagle or is he crossing America on a lawn mower?
夫人 我们现在迫切需要有人在法庭上
Ma'am, we really ought to get someone in court right away
申请限制令延长最后期限
to file a Hail Mary injunction to extend the deadline,
至少拖到我们找到漏掉的选票
someone who can stall till we find the ballots.
我考虑过了
I already thought about that.
不用担心
I've got it covered.
然后侍女过来
So the lady-in-waiting came over to us
跟我们说 "女王陛下
and she said, "Her Majesty
请你们参观她的王冠"
thought perhaps you would like to see her crown."
能想象么 一个阿拉巴马州伯明翰的小男孩
Imagine a shy kid from Birmingham, Alabama,
和英国女王...
and the Queen of England...
女士们 先生们 让我们欢迎美国总统
Ladies and gentlemen, the President of the United States.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
谢谢 看看你
Thank you. Oh, look at that.
蓝灰色的裙子真好看啊?
That's sort of a grey-blue dress. Isn't that something?
你好啊 在内华达状态很好啊
Hi, feeling good in Nevada.
内心振奋内华达啊 你好
Nifty in Nevada. Hi.
- 你太美了 - 我得喝一杯
- You look fantastic. - Yeah, I need a drink.
极需喝一杯 大家快坐下吧
Indeed I do. Everybody, please, sit down.
我等不及要听听那个什么…
I am so excited to hear all about the...
剑龙 披甲植食者
Stegosaurus, the armored plant eater.
- 剑龙 披甲... 盖瑞? - 您需要什么?
- Stegosaurus, the arm... Gary? - Mm-hmm.
我从车队过来的路上把口红弄丢了
I dropped my lipstick somewhere between here and the motorcade.
- 不用担心 我这有一支 - 不要这支 你去把那支找回来
- Okay, I got one right here. - No, go get that one.
- 这就去 - 我都错过了什么?
- Uh-huh. - So what did I miss?
盖瑞刚刚给我们讲了见英国女王的事
We just heard a lovely story about the Queen of England.
她就是个臭婊子
She's a fucking cunt.
- 不是我告诉你的 - 当然
- You didn't hear it from me. - No.
内华达最高法院
票选认证听证会
我们还没找到那些票 你需要再拖一会
We're still searching for the votes, so we need you to stall.
艾米 法庭神圣不可侵犯
Amy, I respect the sanctity
我做不到什么"拖延"
of this courtroom far too much to "Stall."
这个案子简单的一目了然
This is a simple and straightforward case.
不过 这也让它如此复杂
Although, in many ways, that's what makes it so complicated.
- 你看... - 就这么做 不错
- You see... - That's good. Do that.
本庭将审理梅耶与内华达的案件
The court will hear the matter of Meyer v. Nevada,
关于延期重数的提议
a motion to delay certification.
开始之前 请允许我对几个关键词进行定义
Before we begin, I would love to define a few key terms.
选票 一张选票是什么呢?
Vote. What is a vote?
我觉得答案显而易见吧
Well, I think that's pretty obvious.
您确定么 法官大人?
Oh, is it, Your Honor?
投票这个词在不同文化背景中有着许多含义
In many cultures, the word vote can mean a myriad of things.
可以指庆典
It can mean a celebration.
篝火旁的跳舞
It can mean a dance around a fire.
或者静默的点头
It can mean a silent nod.
现在在这 它的含义是什么?
In this room, what does it mean?
有叽嘎麦吉的消息么?
Any news on Creaky McGee?
我们需要找到鲍勃 必须赶在...
Seriously, we have got to find Bob before...
快看这个 把你拍的多好看 还有这张
Look at this. How beautiful you look. And check this out.
快拿开 有那个内达华警察的消息么?
No, no. What about the Nevada State Police?
- 夫人 什么消息都没有 - 没事了 他来了
- Ma'am, there's nothing. - Oh, never mind. We got him.
您说什么? 他来哪了?
What? Where is he?
- 这儿 - 早上好啊
- Here. - Good morning.
鲍勃
Hi, Bob.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hey. - Hi.
见到你真是太棒了
I am so happy to see you.
今天有什么汤?
What kind of soup do you have today?
你想喝什么样的汤?
Um, what kind of soup is on your mind?
那今天星期几了?
Well, what is today?
- 嗯... 星期四 - 今天星期四
- Um... it's Thursday. - It's Thursday.
- 星期四? - 没错
- Thursday? - Yup.
那就是海军豆 美味极了
Navy bean. So delicious.
夫人 您需要... 嘿 鲍勃
Ma'am, you want to... hey, Bob.
我是鲍勃·布拉德利 先生 见到你很高兴
Bob Bradley. Nice to meet you, sir.
- 找到漏票了 - 你确定?
- They found the ballots. - Seriously?
- 是的 - 请等一下 鲍勃
- Yeah. - Excuse me, Bob.
内华达的即时新闻
Breaking news out of Nevada.
根据线报 美国司法部门人员
Acting on a tip, US Justice Department deputies
找到了上星期总统大选时
found an estimated 10,000 uncounted mail-in ballots
- 邮寄的约一万封没有计数的投票... - 这也行
- from last week's presidential election... - Come on.
...于此人家中
...in the house of this man,
54岁的美国邮局职员万斯·奥特罗
54-year-old US postal worker Vance Otlow.
- 你看他 - 从去年邮局
- Look at this guy. - Otlow had grown more erratic
被梅耶邮政委员会关闭停业后
following post office closures last year
奥特罗变得十分不稳定
by the Meyer Postal Commission.
一万张票!
10,000 ballots!
还是个有着高度实用性
From a district with an
统计学价值经验的行政区
empirically high applied demography value.
你说的我一个字也没听懂
I don't know what you're saying,
不过你就继续做那些算术的东西 肯特
but you keep doing that math stuff, Kent,
- 就算谁用这事取笑你也不用管 - 好的 夫人
- no matter how much anyone makes fun of you, okay? - Yes, ma'am.
好极了 都听我说 凯伦
All right, listen. Karen
必须让这些票数得到承认 做得到么?
has got to get those ballots admitted, right?
她会的 不然就换人
She will or she won't.
艾米 我知道这几天不是很尽如人意
Amy, I know the last couple days have not been ideal.
完全糟透了 夫人
To say the least, ma'am.
我希望你明白
I just want you to know
多亏了理查德我才能解决这些问题
that I could not have done it without Richard
一定一定要转达我的感激
and I want you to please relay my thanks to him.
马上就办
I'll get right on that.
夫人 我们在中国的大使打来的
Uh, ma'am, from our ambassador in China.
恐怕中国人
As I feared, the Chinese
开始回应您之前的制裁威胁了
are responding to your threat of sanctions.
一分钟的轻松都不能给我么?
Can I not have just one minute to enjoy this?
我问问那些中国人
I'll ask the Chinese.
法官大人 我刚得到消息
Your Honors, I have just been informed
在瓦肖县找到了那些未经统计的投票表
that uncounted ballots have been discovered in Washoe County.
我申请重新统计票数
I'd like to move that those be included in the recount.
反对 最后期限已经过去了
Objection, the deadline has already passed.
法官大人 我想请问对方如何定义"最后期限"和"过去"?
Your Honor, how is counsel defining "Deadline" And "Passed"?
法官大人 反对!
Your Honor, objection!
推迟期限
The deadline will be extended
直到我们重新审理
until we can hear on this matter.
明早十点再继续
We will reconvene tomorrow at 10:00 A.M.
经过今天发生于内华达的震惊事件
After today's stunning turn of events in Nevada,
总统已决定聘请雄鹰鲍勃·布拉德利
the president has asked Bob Bradley, the Eagle,
返回华盛顿担任她新的
to return to Washington as her new
网络安全主管 立即生效
cybersecurity czar, effective immediately.
同时国务院报告称
Also the State Department is reporting
中国政府
the Chinese government
宣布了一系列针对美国的政策
announced a series of measures aimed at the US.
包括美国出口中国的新限制令
New restrictions on American imports into China,
冻结中国境内的美国投资基金
freezing of US investment funds in China...
对美国公民领养外籍儿童的禁令
a ban on all foreign adoptions by American citizens.
- 以及一些其他的政策 - 迈克! 迈克!
- A bunch of other stuff. - Mike! Mike!
总统会进一步对中国制裁么?
Will the president move forward with her sanctions?
无可奉告
I don't know.
我得打给我老婆
I have to call my wife.
我之前都不知道还有个下层地下室
I didn't know there was a subbasement.
- 特别凉爽 - 确实不错
- Nice and cool. - Yeah, it's nice.
- 这储备了很多物资 - 给我准备的么?
- A lot of supplies here. - This is mine, right?
- 当然了 - 我的天呐
- Oh, yeah. - Oh, boy.
就是这了 雄鹰 你的新巢
And here we go, Eagle, your new nest.
这是不是没有手机信号啊
Now, I don't think my cell phone's gonna work here.
- 猜对了 好好玩吧 - 好极了
- No. Good luck. - Great.
谢了 操后门的
Thanks, buttfucker.